downloadfreepdf.com 2018-05-13

# Privacy Policy - DownloadFreePdf

At DownloadFreepdf.com we are committed to providing you information tailored to your individual wants and needs. We also recognize the importance of protecting personally identifiable information relating to you, our users and subscribers. DownloadFreepdf.com does not collect personally identifying information about individuals, except when specifically and knowingly provided by such individuals. When you enter a contest or other promotional feature, we may request your name, street, and e-mail address to aid in our administration of the contest and to assist in contacting the winners. 

DownloadFreepdf.com utilizes specialized “Server Software” to automatically collect information about which pages each user visits as well as the user’s Internet Service Provider (e.g., aol.com). This information is used for internal review, to tailor information to individual visitors and for traffic audits. 

Under no circumstances will we give specific, identifiable information about our users to outside third parties. However, we will, from time to time, provide advertisers or potential advertisers with aggregated, anonymous information about our users. In addition, any personally identifiable information provided by subscribers as part of an advertiser promotion within one of our partner sites may be provided to such advertisers as needed for the reasonable administration of the promotion. We also reserve the right to amend these policies at any time by updating this page so check back often as your right may change ongoing. we reserve the right to sell our business and in some cases that may include data that is gathered at our websites If this is the case you will receive an initial opt out message from new management and at that time may opt out of further messages. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve our ads on the Internet. These third-party advertising companies employ cookie and 1×1 pixel .gif technology to measure and improve the effectiveness of ads for their clients. To do so, these companies may use anonymous information about your visits to our Web site and other Web sites. This information can include: date/time of banner ad shown, the banner ad that was shown, their cookie, the IP address. This information can also be used for online preference marketing purposes. 

If you want to prevent a third-party advertiser from setting and/or reading cookies on your computer, currently you may either visit each ad network’s web site individually and opt out or visit the NAI gateway opt-out site to opt-out of all network advertising cookies. [Click Here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp) for the NAI gateway opt-out site. This site will also allow you to review the third-party advertising companies’ privacy policies. 

A user’s personally identifiable information (e.g., name, e-mail address) may be required in certain instances. For example, if we run competitions or contests on the site, you may be required to provide information such as your address in order to participate. The exact rules may vary in each case but the specific rules for any contest will state how that information may be used. We may also use personally identifiable information for marketing and promotional purposes. DownloadFreepdf.com may send you e-mail alerting you to new features, products, promotions, or services pertaining to our site. 

We do not control the privacy policies of our business partners, advertisers, sponsors or other sites to which we provide hyperlinks. Users should also be aware that, when you voluntarily disclose personal information in chat areas, bulletin boards, or other public forums, such information may be collected by others and may result in the receipt of unsolicited messages. 

_Children_ : Be sure to ask your parents for permission before you send any information about yourself – like your name, address, or e-mail address – over the Internet, to us or to anyone else and before making any purchases online. 

_Parents_ : We encourage you to get involved with your children’s online usage and to be aware of the activities in which they are participating. We will not knowingly gather personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13 when at all possible. 

Anonymous aggregated data is sometimes provided to other parties which we do business with, for statistical and market research purposes as described above.

Finally you should be aware that if your child voluntarily discloses his or her name, e-mail address, etc. within various public forums (including bulletin boards and chat rooms), such disclosures may result in unsolicited messages from other parties.

Technology on the Internet is developing at a fever pace. It is critical that DownloadFreepdf.com maintain its ability to rapidly adjust these policies in the future. By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by DownloadFreepdf.com. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

**Third Party Advertising**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (NOT including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [Click Here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp)

Third Party Cookies In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser. DownloadFreepdf.com welcomes your questions and comments about privacy. Please send e-mail to [info@DownloadFreepdf.com](mailto:info@DownloadFreepdf.com)
